



in fernandezdaniel85

**+34 640782812** 

☑ dfzfz7@gmail.com

# DANIEL FERNANDEZ

#### ANDROID AND JAVA DEVELOPER

+ INNOVATION AND MANAGEMENT IN TOURISM

#### ABOUT ME

Self-motivated Developer committed to pursuing a career change in the IT sector. Offering 17 years of experience in tourism and hospitality, and having lived and worked in different countries, adapts quickly to changes and environments. Curious, creative and flexible team player who enjoys learning new skills and expanding his knowledge.



Java Spring

Android

MySQL MongoDB

Firebase

HTML CSS

JavaScript

Unity 3DS Max





- · Attentive · Empathetic ·
- · Proactive · Curious ·
- · Self-Motivated · Creative ·
- · Flexible · Team Player ·

### LANGUAGES

Spanish, Catalan (Mother tongue) English (Advanced - CAE) German, Italian (Intermediate - A2)

Russian, French - (Basic - A1)

## **INTERESTS**

#Travel #Gastronomy

#Trekking #Cycling

#eCommerce #Blockchain

#Virtual Reality

## **EDUCATION**

2020 APPLIED VIRTUAL REALITY COURSE (250H)

November 2020 – Currently studying Indústria 4.0 - Santa Perpètua de Mogoda (Spain)

Unity + 3DS Max

2020 A JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER COURSE (350H)

June 2020 – November 2020

IT Academy - Cibernàrium - Barcelona Activa (Spain)

· Java + Spring + MySQL + MongoDB

2020 MASTER'S IN MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

September 2016 – January 2020

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya – UOC (Online)

Android + Firebase + HTML + CSS + JS + Angular

2015 MASTER'S IN INNOVATION AND MANAGEMENT IN TOURISM

Septembre 2012 – February 2015

Salzburg University of Applied Sciences (Austria)

Experience Design + eTourism + Entrepreneurship

2011 BACHELOR'S IN TOURISM STUDIES

Septembre 2006 - July 2011

University of Girona (Spain)

Destination + Hospitality Management

2009 BUSINESS MANAGEMENT COURSE (ERASMUS)

September 2008 - June 2009

Plantijn Hogeschool Antwerpen (Belgium)

· Business + Project Management

## work experience

2011

2011

2020 JR. JAVA DEVELOPER @ IT ACADEMY – BCN ACTIVA (Spain)
October 2015 – November 2020

Backend Development APP and API (Project)

2020 GUEST SERVICE @ THE SERRAS HOTEL BARCELONA (Spain)

April 2015 – February 2020

Lobby, reception and concierge tasks.

2019 CHAUFFEUR/CHASSEUR @ KULM HOTEL ST. MORITZ (Switzerland)

December 2018 – April 2019 (Winter Season)

Lobby, chauffeur, porter, and concierge tasks.

2015 VOLUNTEER @ BERLIN HOSTERIA (Ecuador)

August 2014 – January 2015

Landscaping, gardening, animal care, website.

2014 • F&B ATTENDANT @ NH SALZBURG CITY (Austria)

December 2012 – April 2014

F&B at bar, restaurant, room service and meetings.

2012 FRONT OFFICE @ SHERATON PRAGUE (Czech Republic)

November 2011 – September 2012

Front Office tasks, information, and problem solving.

FRONT OFFICE @ SHERATON AMSTERDAM (Netherlands)

February 2011 – July 2011

Front Office tasks, information, and problem solving.

F&B ATTENDANT @ HOTEL INDALO PARK (Spain) Summers 2002 – 2011

F&B at bar, restaurant, lounge and terrace.